A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CATHARINE ZAHAROV, ET AL. BY HELEN WOOLLARD, ET AL., 1953-1954, 2-TL, 5-D, 2-TLS, 1-NEWSCLIP, 2-N (Box-folder 233:008)
- WORK CONFERENCE ON TUBERCULOSIS NURSING BY HELEN WOOLARD, ET AL., 1952-1953, 3-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 233:009)
- WORLD HEALTH ORGRANIZATION, 1964-1965, 12-D (Box-folder 233:010)
- WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION, -1949, 20-D, 4-TL, 2-N, 4-TLS, 1-N (Box-folder 233:011)
- X-RAY FOR FOOD HANDLERS, TEACHERS, AND OTHER PERSONNEL BY HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1955-1958, 2-N, 3-D, 4-TLS, 1-ALS, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 233:012)
- X-RAY SURVEYS--SCHEDULES, 1952-1953, 1-NEWSCLIP, 3-D (Box-folder 233:013)
- X-RAY CASSETTE BY R.C. WILSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., -1949, 11-D, 1-TLS, 3-pam (Box-folder 233:014)
- X-RAY HOSPITAL PATIENTS AND PERSONNEL, -1949, 8-D, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 233:015)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA BLOCH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: YOUTH BOARD PRESIDENTS, SPONSORS, AND MEMBERS, ET, 1979-1980, 2-TLS, 15-D (Box-folder 233:016)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1978-1979, 9-N, 1-TL, 1-pam, 12-DS, 22-D, 1-AD (Box-folder 234:001)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1977-1978, 25-D, 9-N, 7-DS, 5-TL, 2-TLS, 1-AD (Box-folder 234:002)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1976-1977, 8-N, 30-D, 3-TL, 1-NEWSCLIP, 2-TLS (Box-folder 234:003)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1975-1976, 36-D, 9-N, 2-TL, 2-TLS, 1-DS (Box-folder 234:004)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1974-1975, 40-D, 1-ALS, 7-N, 8-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 234:005)
- YOUTH BOARD BY VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION, 1973-1974, 37-D, 4-TL, 6-N, 1-DS, 1-ALS (Box-folder 234:006)
- VIRGINIA TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YOUTHBOARD, 1972-1973, 61-D, 6-pam, 20-N, 1-AD, 5-TL, 2-ALS, 1-TLS (Box-folder 235:001)
- VIRGINIA TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YOUTH BOARD, 1971-1972, 27-D, 3-TLS, 4-TL, 1-ALS, 4-N (Box-folder 235:002)
- VTRDA YOUTH BOARD, 1969-1970, 31-D, 4-N, 3-pam, 1-AD, 1-TL, 2-TLS, 1-ALS (Box-folder 235:003)
- YOUTH BOARD MINUTES, 1969-1979, 33-D (Box-folder 235:004)
- YOUTH PROGRAM COMMITTEE, 1973-1979, 28-D, 2-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 235:005)
- VIRGINIA TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YOUTH BOARD, 1970-1971, 32-D, 8-N, 8-TLS, 1-AN, 1-NEWSCLIP, 6-TL, 1-DS (Box-folder 235:006)
- YOUTH BOARD NEWSLETTERS--PHANTASMAGORIA--MAILING SCHEDULE, 1976-1977, 14-D (Box-folder 235:007)
- YOUTH BOARD NEWSLETTER--PHANTASMAGORIA--MAILING SCHEDULE, 1970-1974, 33-D (Box-folder 235:008)
- PHANTASMAGORIA NEWSLETTER, 1970-1977, 26-D (Box-folder 235:009)
- ZAHAROV, MRS. CATHARINE BY MRS. J. YORK WELBORN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRED MITCHELL, ET AL., 1959-1965, 11-D, 61-TL, 12-TLS, 11-c.d.s, 5-N, 21-ALS, 1-AN, 3-DS (Box-folder 236:001)
- ZAHAROV, CATHARINE CARTER AWARD--NOMINATIONS, 1975-1978, 9-D (Box-folder 236:002)
- DOCUMENTED YEAR END REPORTS RECEIVED, 1969-1970, 5-D (Box-folder 236:003)
- BLUE RIDGE TB ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORTS, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 11-D, 9-map (Box-folder 236:004)
- ROANOKE AREA TB AND RD ASSOCATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 7-D, 5-map (Box-folder 236:005)
- CENTERAL VIRGINIA TB ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 13-D, 11-map (Box-folder 236:006)
- MOUNTAIN EMPIRE TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 11-D, 8-map (Box-folder 236:007)
- PIEDMONT TB AND RD ASSOICATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 4-D, 4-map (Box-folder 236:008)
- SHENDOAH TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 1-AD, 6-D, 6-map (Box-folder 236:009)
- SOUTHSIDE TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1966?, 9-D, 8-map (Box-folder 237:001)
- SOUTHWEST TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING ARE, 1964?, 1-N, 8-D, 8-map (Box-folder 237:002)
- TIDEWATER TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, STATISTICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1968, 15-D, 13-map (Box-folder 237:003)
- TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN VIRGINIA YEAR END REPORT, STATISICAL AND GENERAL INFORMATION CONCERNING AREAS, 1964, 9-D, 8-map (Box-folder 237:004)
- BLUE RIDGE TB ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971-1972, 1-N, 2-D (Box-folder 237:005)
- CENTERAL VIRGINIA TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971, 1-pam, 1-N, 12-D (Box-folder 237:006)
- MOUTNAIN EMPIRE TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971, 1-N, 2-D (Box-folder 237:007)
- TIDEWATER TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1970-1971, 3-N, 3-TLS, 2-DS, 2-pam, 18-D (Box-folder 237:008)
- POTOMAC TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT BY E.R. SEWARD, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 4-N, 12-D, 2-DS, 1-TLS (Box-folder 237:009)
- RICHMOND AREA TB ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1970-1971, 1-N, 2-DS, 13-D (Box-folder 237:010)
- ROANOKE AREA TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971-1972, 10-D, 1-pam, 1-N, 2-DS (Box-folder 238:001)
- SHENANDOAH TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971-1972, 2-D, 1-N (Box-folder 238:002)
- SOUTHEASTERN VIRGINIA TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1970-1972, 8-D, 4-pam, 1-N, 3-DS (Box-folder 238:003)
- SOUTHERN TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971-1972, 4-D, 1-pam, 1-N, 2-DS (Box-folder 238:004)
- SOUTHSIDE TB AND HEALTH ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1971-1972, 2-D, 1-N, 1-pam (Box-folder 238:005)
- SOUTHWEST TB AND RD ASSOCIATION YEAR END REPORT, 1970-1971, 2-D (Box-folder 238:006)
- BLUE RIDGE TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY CATHARINE GIBBS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 47-N (Box-folder 238:007)
- BLUE RIDGE TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY CATHARINE GIBBS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W WENDT, ET AL., 1969-1971, 48-N, 1-D (Box-folder 238:008)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA TB-RD ASSOCIATIONS, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY EMMA ANTHONY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 4-N, 2-D (Box-folder 238:009)
- PIEDMONT TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY MARY TUCKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1970-1971, 11-N (Box-folder 238:010)
- PIEDMONT TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY MARY TUCKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1969-1970, 7-N (Box-folder 238:011)
- ROANOKE AREA TUBERCULOSIS AND RESPIRATORY DISEASE ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY MRS. WILLIAM MURRAY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1972-1973, 5-N, 12-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 238:012)
- SHENANDOAH TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY VIRGINIA LINDAMOOD, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 1-N, 14-D (Box-folder 238:013)
- SOUTHSIDE VA TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY ANNIE WOOD TAYLOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 4-N (Box-folder 238:014)
- SOUTHSIDE VA TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY ANNIE WOOD TAYLOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1970-1971, 42-N (Box-folder 238:015)
- SOUTHSIDE VA TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY ANNIE WOOD TAYLOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1969-1970, 33-N, 2-pam, 1-D (Box-folder 239:001)
- SOUTHWEST VRIGINIA TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY ROBERT HELTON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1970-1971, 5-N (Box-folder 239:002)
- SOUTHWEST VA TB-RD ASSOCIATION, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS BY ROBERT HELTON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1969-1970, 10-D, 8-N (Box-folder 239:003)
- TB-RD ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN VIRGINIA BY FLORENCE MORRISON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1971-1972, 10-N (Box-folder 239:004)
- TB-RD OF NORTHERN VIRGINIA, WEEKLY FIELD REPORTS, 1970-1971, 7-N, 3-D (Box-folder 239:005)
- ALA DETAILS, 1980, 18-D (Box-folder 239:006)
- ALA DETAILS, 1980, 25-D, 2-pam (Box-folder 239:007)
- ALA DETAILS, 1980, 13-D (Box-folder 239:008)
- ALA DETAILS, 1979, 3-D (Box-folder 240:001)
- ALA UPDATE, 1980, 48-D (Box-folder 240:002)
- ALA UPDATE, 1979, 46-D (Box-folder 240:003)
- ALA UPDATE, 1978, 44-D (Box-folder 240:004)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1970, 3-D (Box-folder 240:005)
- VLA BULLETIN, 1973, 11-D (Box-folder 240:006)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1972, 18-D (Box-folder 240:007)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1971, 11-D (Box-folder 240:008)
- VTRA BULLETIN, 1970, 18-D (Box-folder 240:009)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1969, 19-D (Box-folder 240:010)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1968, 17-D (Box-folder 241:001)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1967, 18-D (Box-folder 241:002)
- VTRDA BULLETIN, 1966, 6-D (Box-folder 241:003)
- Biographical Information: Albert, Eddie ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:001)
  biography
- Biographical Information: Albert, Guilda M. ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:002)
- Biographical Information: Allred, Charlene Ann ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:003)
  CV
- Biographical Information: Almond, J. Lindsey ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:004)
- Biographical Information: Anderegg, James A. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:005)
  Biographical information form
- Biographical Information: Anderson, Daniel N. ND, 4-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 242:006)
- Biographical Information: Anderson, Robert John ND, 1-photo, 5-TD (Box-folder 242:007)
  CVs, Biographies, Biography Briefs
- Biographical Information: Anderson, William H. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:008)
- Biographical Information: Anthonison, N. R. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:009)
- Biographical Information: Anthony, Emma G. ND, 1-photo, 1-negative, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:010)
- Biographical Information: Anthony, M. V. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:011)
  letter(CV)
- Biographical Information: Apperson, William E. ND, 3-photos, 3-negatives, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:012)
- Biographical Information: Arey, Richard Walton ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:013)
- Biographical Information: Armstrong, Floyd ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:014)
- Biographical Information: Askew, Nancy ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:015)
- Biographical Information: Atkinson, Mary Louise ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:016)
- Biographical Information: Auerbach, Oscar ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:017)
- Biographical Information: Auffant, Roberto Antonio ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:018)
- Biographical Information: Ayres, Stephen M. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:019)
- Biographical Information: Bachtell, Clifton Merle Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:020)
- Biographical Information: Bacon, Nathaniel ND, 2-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 242:021)
- Biographical Information: Bageant, Robert Allen ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:022)
- Biographical Information: Bagley, Philip J. III ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:023)
- Biographical Information: Bailey, Pearl ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:024)
- Biographical Information: Baird, F. S. ND, 1-AD,1-TD (Box-folder 242:025)
  Biographical Information Form, Recruitment Pamphlet
- Biographical Information: Baker, Cathy (Purcell) ND, 2-photos, 2-TD, 1-AD (Box-folder 242:026)
- Biographical Information: Baker, James Porter ND, 10-photos, 1-negative, 3-TD, 1-AD (Box-folder 242:027)
  CV, letter(CV), Biographical Information Form
- Biographical Information: Barden, Tina ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:028)
- Biographical Information: Bartlett, Albert Charles ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:029)
- Biographical Information: Barlow, Peter B. ND, 2-phots, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:030)
- Biographical Information: Barnes, Robert Webster ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:031)
- Biographical Information: Barnwell, Margaret Walker ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:032)
  Biographical Information Form
- Biographical Information: Barrie, Robb ND, 3-photos (Box-folder 242:033)
- Biographical Information: Battle, John ND, 3-photos (Box-folder 242:034)
- Biographical Information: Bean, William J. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:035)
- Biographical Information: Beard, James Taylor ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:036)
- Biographical Information: Beck, G. Gordon ND, 1-AD, 1-newspaper clipping(photocopy) (Box-folder 242:037)
- Biographical Information: Becque, William ND, 3-TD (Box-folder 242:038)
  letter, letter(Biography), Report(Biography)
- Biographical Information: Bell, George ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:039)
- Biographical Information: Berry, Frederick Aroyce, Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:040)
- Biographical Information: Bierley, Connie ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:041)
- Biographical Information: Birchler, Mary Anne ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:042)
- Biographical Information: Bissell, Emily P. ND, 1-photo, 3-stamps, 1-poster (Box-folder 242:043)
- Biographical Information: Blackman, Raymond S. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:044)
- Biographical Information: Blaylock, Norma ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:045)
- Biographical Information: Blide, Richard Wayne ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:046)
- Biographical Information: Bliss, Suzanne R. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:047)
- Biographical Information: Bloch, Mrs. Virginia ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:048)
- Biographical Information: Boehlecke, Brian A. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:049)
- Biographical Information: Bokel, Elizabeth A. ND, 1-AD (Box-folder 242:050)
- Biographical Information: Booberg, Carl Campbell ND, 3-photos, 1-AD (Box-folder 242:051)
- Biographical Information: Bookman, Ada Mae (Sandy) ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:052)
- Biographical Information: Bosher, William B. Cleveland, Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:053)
- Biographical Information: Bourhill, Graham H. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:054)
- Biographical Information: Bowman, Richard T. ND, 1-photo, 3-TD (Box-folder 242:055)
  CVs, Biography
- Biographical Information: Boyd, Clarissa E. ND, 2-photos, 2-TD (Box-folder 242:056)
  Biographies
- Biographical Information: Brantigan, Otto C. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:057)
- Biographical Information: Braun, Warren L. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:058)
- Biographical Information: Braxton, Lelia ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:059)
- Biographical Information: Brickman, Robert D. ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 242:060)
  CV, Speaker Confirmation Form
- Biographical Information: Broecker, Frederick H. ND, 6-photos, 3-TD (Box-folder 242:061)
  CV, Biographies
- Biographical Information: Brown, E. Donald ND, 1-AD (Box-folder 242:062)
- Biographical Information: Brown, James M. ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:063)
- Biographical Information: Brown, Otis L. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:064)
  Biography
- Biographical Information: Brown, Sam C. Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:065)
- Biographical Information: Browning Eleanor Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:066)
- Biographical Information: Brummer, Donald L. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:067)
- Biographical Information: Brunk, James R. Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:068)
- Biographical Information: Bunch, Harold ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 242:069)
- Biographical Information: Burcher, L. Manning ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:070)
- Biographical Information: Burke, George Wilson III ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:071)
- Biographical Information: Busse, William F. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 242:072)
- Biographical Information: Buttery, C. M. G. ND, 1-photo, 2-TD (Box-folder 242:073)
  CV, Biographical Information Form
- Biographical Information: Burkhardt, Dorothy ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 242:074)
  Biographical Information Form, Biography
- Biographical Information: Cake, Charles Powell ND, 2-photos, 1-newspaper clippings(photocopy), 3-TD (Box-folder 243:001)
- Biographical Information: Camp, Paul D. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:002)
- Biographical Information: Campbell, Don ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:003)
- Biographical Information: Campbell, Louise ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:004)
- Biographical Information: Campbell, Winston ND, 1-phot (Box-folder 243:005)
- Biographical Information: Carpenter, Carol ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:006)
- Biographical Information: Carpenter, M. Scott ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:007)
- Biographical Information: Carr, David Turner ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:008)
- Biographical Information: Carson ND, 1-photo, 1-negative (Box-folder 243:009)
- Biographical Information: Caruthers, Preston C. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:010)
- Biographical Information: Chalker, William R. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:011)
- Biographical Information: Cake, ND, 2-photos, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:012)
- Biographical Information: Chapman, W. Holmes, Jr. ND, 2-photos, 1-Biography (Box-folder 243:012)
- Biographical Information: Christian, Marilyn J. ND, 1-AD (Box-folder 243:013)
- Biographical Information: Clark, DR. ND, 1-photo, 1-negative (Box-folder 243:014)
- Biographical Information: Clyde, Wallace Jr. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:015)
- Biographical Information: Colley, Roberta Davis ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:016)
- Biographical Information: Colden, C. M. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:017)
- Biographical Information: Cooke, William L. ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 243:018)
- Biographical Information: Cooper, Kevin R. ND, 2-newspaper clippings(photocopy), 3-TD (Box-folder 243:019)
  CV, Biography, Questionnaire Answers
- Biographical Information: Copper, William ND, 2-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 243:020)
- Biographical Information: Copping, Taylor R. ND, 9-photos, 4-negatives, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:021)
- Biographical Information: Cordell, Alfred Robert ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:022)
- Biographical Information: Corwin, Emil ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:023)
- Biographical Information: Cowley, Michael Joseph ND, 3-TD (Box-folder 243:024)
  CVs, Speaker Confirmation Form
- Biographical Information: Crawley, Fannie ND, 1-AD (Box-folder 243:025)
- Biographical Information: Crisler, Crile ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:026)
- Biographical Information: Critzer, Ben ND, 2-photos (Box-folder 243:027)
- Biographical Information: Crockett, Walter ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:028)
- Biographical Information: Cross, Shelia ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:029)
  Resume
- Biographical Information: Crumbliss, Larry ND, 1-photo, 1-negative (Box-folder 243:030)
- Biographical Information: Cutts, Dorothea ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:031)
- Biographical Information: Cutts, Richard M. ND, 6-newspaper clippings(photocopy) (Box-folder 243:032)
- Biographical Information: Dabney, Virginia B. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:033)
- Biographical Information: Daniel, Donald S. Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:034)
- Biographical Information: Daniel, Griffith ND, 7-photos (Box-folder 243:035)
- Biographical Information: Cake, ND, 2-photos, 1-newspaper clippings(photocopy), 3-TD (Box-folder 243:001)
- Biographical Information: Daniel, John Moncure, Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:036)
- Biographical Information: Daughtry, DeWitt C. ND, 1-TD, 1-AD (Box-folder 243:037)
  Biographical Information Forms
- Biographical Information: Davidson, Gilbert ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:038)
- Biographical Information: Davidson, Kate Saunders ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:039)
- Biographical Information: Davies, Baubhenel ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:040)
- Biographical Information: Davis, George ND, 2-photos (Box-folder 243:041)
- Biographical Information: Derring, Eldridge Hopkins, Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:042)
- Biographical Information: DeShazo, Charles, Mrs. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:043)
- Biographical Information: Dicke, James L. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:044)
  CV, Biography
- Biographical Information: DiMarco, John Philip ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:045)
- Biographical Information: DiMeo, Michael Joseph ND, 5-TD (Box-folder 243:046)
  CV, Letters, Speaker Confirmation Form
- Biographical Information: Donovan, H. A. ND, 1-photo, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 243:047)
- Biographical Information: Donowitz, Leigh Grossman ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:048)
- Biographical Information: Downey, L. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:049)
- Biographical Information: Doyle, Hugh J. III ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 243:050)
- Biographical Information: Doyle, Margaret P. ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 243:051)
  CVs
- Biographical Information: Draper, David Adrian ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:052)
- Biographical Information: Draper, Walter ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:053)
- Biographical Information: Drash, Elizabeth H. ND, 1-photo, 1-AD (Box-folder 243:054)
- Biographical Information: Drash, Everett Cato ND, 11-photos, 2-negatives, 2-AD, 2-TD, 2-newspaper clippings (Box-folder 243:055)
  Biographical Information Form, Biographies
- Biographical Information: Drash, Robert A. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 243:056)
- Biographical Information: Dunbar, Frank P. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:057)
- Biographical Information: Durbin, Charles Gaskill Jr. ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 243:058)
- Biographical Information: Edelman, Barbara ND, 1-photo, 2-TD (Box-folder 243:059)
  CV, Letter
- Biographical Information: Edmondson, William Pagon Jr. ND, 3-TD (Box-folder 243:060)
  CV, Report, Biographical Information Form
- Biographical Information: Eggleston, Peyton Archer ND, 8-photos, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:061)
- Biographical Information: Eisenberg, Stuart Jerome ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:062)
- Biographical Information: Elmore, Laura H. ND, 2-photos, 1-TD, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 243:063)
- Biographical Information: Engledove, Mrs. Giles C. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:064)
- Biographical Information: Ewart, George E. ND, 3-photos, 1-negative, 1-newspaper clipping, 1-TD (Box-folder 243:065)
- Biographical Information: Fairly, John L. Jr. ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:001)
- Biographical Information: Fairman, Ralph Paul ND, 3-TD (Box-folder 244:002)
- Biographical Information: Dr. Fasoli ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:003)
- Biographical Information: Dr.Feldmann ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:004)
- Biographical Information: Ferris, Benjamin G. Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:005)
- Biographical Information: Fife, Jerry ND, 1-phot0 (Box-folder 244:006)
- Biographical Information: Finley, Charles O. ND, 2-photos, 1-AD, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:007)
- Biographical Information: Foster, Leslie Comb ND, 3-photos, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:008)
- Biographical Information: Fountain, Herbert ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:009)
- Biographical Information: Frazer, Lucille Lewis ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:010)
- Biographical Information: Freeman, Douglas S. ND, 2-photos (Box-folder 244:012)
- Biographical Information: Fretwell, Jack ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:013)
- Biographical Information: Frik, Seigina M. ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:014)
- Biographical Information: Friddell, Guy ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:015)
- Biographical Information: Fridley, Jackie ND, 1-photo, 1-negative, 1-Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 244:016)
- Biographical Information: Furcolow, Michael L. ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:017)
- Biographical Information: Fussell, James David ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:018)
- Biographical Information: Gaber, Thaddeus ND, 4-photos, 3-negatives, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:019)
- Biographical Information: Gabler, Lee ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:020)
- Biographical Information: Galbraith, Ben ND, 2-photos (Box-folder 244:021)
- Biographical Information: Gallagher, Frances E. ND, 3-photos, 2-negatives, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:022)
- Biographical Information: Gardner, L. H. ND, 1-newspaper clippings(photocopy), 2-TD (Box-folder 244:023)
  Letter(CV), President's Annual Report
- Biographical Information: Garner, Hazel Henderson ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:024)
- Biographical Information: Gassert, Carole Anne ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:025)
- Biographical Information: Gayle, Fleeta ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:026)
- Biographical Information: Gayle, William E. Jr. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:027)
- Biographical Information: Gentry, Wayne ND, 3-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 244:028)
- Biographical Information: Gibbs, Catherine L. ND, 1-photo, 1-negative, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:029)
- Biographical Information: Gibson, Frank J. ND, 1-TD, 1-AD (Box-folder 244:030)
- Biographical Information: Gilbert, Foster I. (Frances B.) ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:031)
- Biographical Information: Gilbert, Warren W. ND, 1-photo (Box-folder 244:032)
- Biographical Information: Gildersleeve, Gerald Alan ND, 1-photo, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:033)
- Biographical Information: Glauser, Frederick Louis ND, 2-TD (Box-folder 244:034)
- Biographical Information: Goldberg, Steven K. ND, 1-TD (Box-folder 244:035)